

### Location

Madrid, Spain

#### **Email**

marta.molina@live.u-tad.com

#### Likedin

@marta-m-aguilera

### **Portfolio**

https://martamagui.github.io

# Languages

Spanish(Native)

English B1-B2

German B1

## Skills

**JavaScript** 

Java

Kotlin

**HTML** 

CSS/Sass

Swift

MySQL

PL/SQL

MongoDB

Git

## Marta Molina Aguilera

### **Junior Developer**

Web, Desktop & Android applications

I am a Multiplatform Apps Development student, but it has been a journey to figure out my way.

I have worked in many areas to find myself as IT Support Teacher right

The coding-world was an exciting adventure waiting to be discovered. I am enjoying each day of this journey. I can not wait for the next thing, I am always craving to learn more.

## **Experience**

Sep 2021 — Present Madrid, Spain

**After-school Support Teacher** (Applications Development)

U-tad (Scholarship assistant due academic performance)

Jan 2019 — Nov 2021

Madrid, Spain

Waitress Alsea S.A.

Mar 2018 — Sept 2018

Madrid, Spain

**DressMaker (Theater Costuming)** 

Taller de Costura Gremar

Sep 2016 — Mar 2018

Madrid, Spain

**Employee** 

BurguerKing Spain S.A.

Aug 2015 — Feb 2016 Reichenbach in Vogtland,

Germany

Forbriger Backwaren GmbH

Mar 2014 — Jul 2014

Madrid, Spain

**DressMaker (Wedding Costuming)** 

Lorenzo Caprile S.L

### **Education**

**Multi-platform Applications Development (CertHE)** 2020 — Present

Pattern making and Fashion (CertHE) 2016 — 2018

IES Santa Engracia

2015

**German B1 TANDEM Escuela Internacional** 

**Customing and Fashion (VET)** 2012 - 2014IES Santa Engracia

**General Certificate of Secondary Education** 2008 - 2012IES La Dehesilla / IES Jaime Ferrán

